Before gangs had guns...they fought with guts.
Deuces Wild is a action, crime, drama film directed by Scott Kalvert.
In 1950s New York City, a bad and bloody gang war is about to erupt on the
dysfunctional streets of Brooklyn between the Deuces and the vicious Vipers.
Leon, played by Stephen Dorff.
Bobby, played by Brad Renfro.
Annie, played by Fairuza Balk.
Marco, played by Norman Reedus.
Freddie, played by Max Perlich.
Betsy, played by Drea De Matteo.
Deuces Wild is a 2002 American crime drama film directed by Scott
Kalvert and written by Paul Kimatian and Christopher Gambale.
The film stars Stephen Dorff, Brad Renfro, James
Franco, Matt Dillon, and Fairuza Balk.
Martin Scorsese was originally the executive producer (as a favor to
Kimatian), but he eventually removed his name from this film.
It was the final film of cinematographer John A.
Alonzo before his death in 2001.
The film explores themes of new york city, gang, drug overdose.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.